savagex.com 2019-10-29

# SAVAGE X FENTY | Lingerie by Rihanna

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) addresses how Lavender Lingerie, LLC ("Lavender Lingerie") collects, protects, and uses information you provide. By visiting www.savagex.com (the "Site"), and providing your information to us, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**What Information Is Collected**  
We group the collection of user information into two categories: personal, which is information identifiable to a specific member, and aggregate, which is general demographic information that does not identify any individual member. Personal information may include your name, username, profile picture, date of birth, email address, mailing address, credit card information, phone number, and any other identifying information you may choose to provide. We may also give you the option to upload or share images or videos of yourself and others on our Site. Additionally, we may collect certain technical information such as your Site preferences as well as demographic information such as size and language preferences, age, gender, geographical location, time zone, income and education. Lavender Lingerie may use or disclose aggregate information for any lawful purpose.

**How We Use Your Information**  
We collect personal information to make our services related to this Site (the "Services") more rewarding for you to use, including billing, shipping and tracking your orders. If we have any questions or concerns regarding your order, we may use this information to contact you. We also use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences and improving customer experience on the Site. We may also use your information to contact you for promotional purposes and provide customer service to you. If you enter into a sweepstakes, contest or similar promotion, we may use the information you provide to administer those activities, email participants, notify winners, and award prizes. By participating in a sweepstakes, contest or similar promotion, you agree to the promotion’s terms and conditions and agree to share the information you submit for the promotion with the sponsors of that promotion. We may combine information about you with information from other sources in order to improve the quality of our Services.

We also receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information, which is collected passively using various technologies, and cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Services. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve you, we often conduct research on customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the personal and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. We may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

As we are part of a global group of companies, by using the Services you acknowledge that we may use the personal information we collect or receive about you in the US, European Economic Area and other countries in which we and our partners operate for purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  This includes sharing your information with other companies in our global group.

**How Is This Information Shared**  
We share information about you only as described in this Privacy Policy and with companies within our global group including, but not limited to, our subsidiaries and affiliates. Our group companies follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy. 

In addition, there are certain circumstances in which we may share your personal information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:  

  * We may share information about you with trusted third parties in order to improve your customer experience. These third parties may contact you about products, services or promotions you may be interested in, or to otherwise improve your customer experience with this Site.

  * We may share information about you, such as your name, address, email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us via our third-party advertising partners and its service providers, in order to deliver to you relevant banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our advertising partners will make the data we provide to it anonymous. To learn more about the use of this information or to make choices about receiving personalized advertising provided by third parties, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices).

  * As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, your information may be part of the transferred assets.

  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of Lavender Lingerie, its users or the public.

  * As required by law, to comply with a judicial proceeding, subpoena or court order, to exercise our rights, or to defend against any claims.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
This Site uses cookies and web beacons to gather aggregated, non-personally identifiable information in order to help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of this Site users have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. Such information may be shared with trusted third parties but the information will not personally identify you. To the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information. As we develop this Site, we may gather additional information from you through the use of other technologies.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to collect anonymous information about how you use this Site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our Site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave our Site. The cookies are not connected to your personal information. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Site's features and disabling may cause some features on the Site to operate improperly.

Lavender Lingerie does not read or respond to “Do Not Track” browser settings and if used, our Site may continue to collect information in the manner indicated in this Privacy Policy.

**Web Beacons**  
Web beacons, or clear gifs, are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. Web beacons help us better manage content on our Site by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to your personal information.

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you provide sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us and to guard against loss, unauthorized access, misuse, disclosure, alteration and destruction, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of such information. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any personal information to us or any other party online. In the event that we learn of a security breach, we may notify you electronically or in writing, to the extent required by law, so you may take appropriate protective steps. If you have any questions about security on our Site, please contact us as indicated below.

**Opting Out**  
We may occasionally send you newsletters and emails regarding announcements, special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates. We may also communicate with you on behalf of third parties about special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates we think may be of interest to you, or you may have opted-in to receive newsletters or special promotions from one of our trusted third party providers. If you decide you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link or by following the instructions included in the communication. You may also opt-out of certain targeted advertising by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). Note, however, that as user of the Services you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Services, such as billing or service notifications.

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Site and does not apply to other sites that are owned and operated by third parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that you disclose to such sites or that they may collect, and you will need to contact the other sites directly for information regarding their privacy policies. The privacy policies of the other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there.

**Public Features of the Site**

This Site may enable you to post comments, reviews, photos, videos, and other information on publicly available areas of this Site. Any information you post in these areas of this Site will be available to all of our users.  By posting on the publicly available areas of the Site, you agree that Lavender Lingerie is not responsible for the information posted or the use of that information by any third party, so please use caution in disclosing any personal information when you post such comments, reviews, photos, videos or other information. We reserve the right to terminate user accounts if the public features of this Site is used inconsistently with the Site’s Terms of Service.

**Accessing, Updating or Deleting Your Online Account Information**  
You may access, update, supplement or correct your online account information at any time by logging into your account and navigating to the "My Account" page or by contacting us. You can also contact us by phone if you wish to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

**Children Under 13**  
This Site is not designed for children and we do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your account. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information online, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us to have that child’s information deleted.  You must be 18 or over to purchase products and provide personal information to this Site.

**Exclusion to This Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Lavender Lingerie through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as review sections and forums (collectively, "Public Areas"), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Lavender Lingerie shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

**California Residents**  
If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to Lavender Lingerie, LLC, Attn: Legal Department, California Shine the Light Inquiry, 800 Apollo Drive, El Segundo, CA 90245.

**NEVADA RESIDENTS**  
If you are a Nevada resident and have provided us with any personal identifying information, you may opt-out of sharing your information with third parties if you submit an opt-out request to the following email address: nevadaprivacy@techstyle.com. Please note we do not sell any of your personal information for profit, we do share some information with contracted third parties in order to provide better services and advertising to you.  Please allow 60 days for competition of such request. 

**EU-US Privacy Shield Program**  
Lavender Lingerie complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Lavender Lingerie has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome>.

**Types of Data Collected Under the EU-US Privacy Shield**  
The following personal data may be collected from EU customers: name, email address, and IP address. This personal data is used for the following purposes: marketing and sales, internal research, and compliance with federal, state and local laws and regulations. Lavender Lingerie also collects aggregate data such as your Site preferences, sizes, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education. This aggregate data is used for the following purposes: marketing and sales activities, to optimize shopping experience and types of goods sold, internal research, partnerships or agreements with affiliates, agents and business partners, and to describe our Services to current and prospective business partners.

**Who We Share Information With Under the EU-US Privacy Shield**  
Lavender Lingerie may disclose personal and non-personally identifiable aggregate data with affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners, advertisers and vendors. The purpose for disclosure to affiliates, subsidiaries and business partners is to improve customer experience, for internal research and marketing and sales purposes. We may share information with advertisers and vendors to comply with lawful agreements and for advertising purposes. Lavender Lingerie retains potential liability in cases of onward transfer of information to third parties.

Lavender Lingerie may also be required to disclose personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Individuals will be notified by Lavender Lingerie in the event it uses or discloses information for a purpose other than that for which the information was originally collected or discloses information to a non-agent third party. Notice may take a variety of forms, including through amendments or modifications to this Privacy Policy.

**Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information**  
You have the right to access, correct or delete personal data which has been provided to Lavender Lingerie. At any time, you may update or correct your online account information by logging into your account and navigating to the "My Account" page or by contacting us. You may also delete your personal data by contacting us to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

If you do not want Lavender Lingerie to use or disclose your information or provide your information to third parties for marketing and sales purposes, please contact Lavender Lingerie at the address provided below under "Inquiries or Complaints Regarding the EU-US Privacy Shield Program". If you have already received a non-administrative communication that you did not wish to receive, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link or by following the instructions included in the communication.

**Inquiries or Complaints Regarding the EU-US Privacy Shield Program**  
In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, Lavender Lingerie commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Lavender Lingerie at:

Lavender Lingerie GmbH  
Attn: Legal Department/Privacy  
38 St Martin’s Lane, Second Floor

WC2N 4ER  
United Kingdom

Lavender Lingerie has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint. There is no charge to consumers for calling or using this independent dispute resolution mechanism.

Under certain limited conditions, European Union individuals may be able to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission.

Lavender Lingerie is subject to the jurisdiction and investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

**Amendments or Modifications to this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Notice of any change will be posted on this Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding the use of our Site or Privacy Policy, please contact us by calling (855) SAVAGEX or by writing to us at:

Lavender Lingerie, LLC

Attn: Legal Department/Privacy  
800 Apollo Street  
El Segundo, CA 90245
